A Guide to the Office of the President, Legal Advisor Office Administrative Files, 1908-1957
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the President, Legal Advisor Office Administrative Files 1908-1957
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/2/1.881
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restricted. Contact author for details.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1989 January 6.
Contents List
- Abbey, Leonard B. 1948 (Box 1)
- Aeronautical Training 1939-1953 (Box 1)
- Akerman, Alfred 1940-1947 (Box 1)
- Alderman 1928-1929 (Box 1)
- Alexander Construction Company, Inc. 1928 (Box 1)
- Alexander, William - Estate 1937-1939 (Box 1)
- Altschul, Benjamin 1932-1933 (Box 1)
- American Railway Express Co. 1924 (Box 1)
- American Type Founders Association 1940-1941 (Box 1)
- Andrew, Eliza J.H. - Estate 1930 (Box 1)
- Art Museum 1933-1935 (Box 1)
- Athletic Department 1935 (Box 1)
- Attorney General 1940 (Box 1)
- Austin, Arthur W. - Estate 1949 (Box 1)
- Autopsies 1945-1947 (Box 1)
- "B" Miscellaneous 1928-1932 (Box 1)
- Baber, W.F. 1946 (Box 1)
- Band 1937-1942 (Box 1)
- Band-Statements 1941-1942 (Box 1)
- Band, University of Virginia-Individual Claims 1941-1942 (Box 1)
- Bennett, Lelia S.-Estate 1925-1926 (Box 2)
- Bird, Dr. R.M.-Estate 1941 (Box 2)
- Board of Visitors 1925-1948 (Box 2)
- Broce, Miss Elizabeth 1921-1922 (Box 2)
- Brown, Waller 1925-1934 (Box 2)
- C.& A. Railway Company 1918 (Box 2)
- Cameron 1935 (Box 2)
- Campbell, Edmund s. 1934-1935 (Box 2)
- Carter, John W. Jr. 1938-1942 (Box 2)
- Carruthers, E.J.-Bursar 1924-1941 (Box 2)
- Cather, Rear Admiral David C. 1945-1947 (Box 2)
- Cellar Restaurant 1938-1943 (Box 2)
- Centennial Endowment 1920-1923 (Box 2)
- Centennial Endowment Fund 1920-1928, 2 folders (Box 3)
- Central Hanover Bank & Trust Co. 1939-1942 (Box 3)
- Centrifuge Patent 1942-1946 (Box 3)
- Chaloner, John Armstrong 1936-1938 (Box 3)
- Chaloner, John Armstrong 1917-1936 (Box 3)
- Chaloner, John Armstrong and Roanoke Rapids School Board 1915-1923 (Box 3)
- Chinn, Ellen Horndon - Estate 1936 (Box 3)
- Chinn, Mrs. Mary Scott - Estate 1945-1946 (Box 3)
- City of Charlottesville [1915] 1931-1932 (Box 4)
- Cobb, Albert Henry 1948-1949 (Box 4)
- Coffinberry, Este - Estate 1921-1941 (Box 4)
- Coles, Walter D. - Estate 1936-1939 (Box 4)
- Collections 1918-1941 (Box 4)
- College Topics and Ivey F. Lewis 1945 (Box 4)
- Conquest, Dunn & Potter 1945 (Box 4)
- Copley Hill 1947-1948 (Box 4)
- Copley Hill and Mrs. Parrott 1949-1950 (Box 4)
- County of Albemarle 1915-1916 (Box 4)
- Covington, Castor 1945 (Box 4)
- Craver, Harry - Estate 1940-1941 (Box 4)
- Crockett, Nathan A.-Estate 1949 (Box 4)
- Dancy, Unity D. - Estate 1932-1942 (Box 5)
- Davis, Miss Carrie Preston 1938-1939 (Box 5)
- Davis, Marguerite B. - Estate 1948 (Box 5)
- Deering, Dorothy - Estate 1945 (Box 5)
- Delta Chi Trust Chapter 1936-1938 (Box 5)
- Delta Chi 1943 (Box 5)
- Dr. Charles M. Fauntleroy Estate 1937-1938 (Box 5)
- Doremus, Robert P. - Estate 1913-1929 (Box 5)
- Dormitories and Academic Building 1928 (Box 5)
- "E" Miscellaneous 1929-1934 (Box 5)
- Edwards, Mrs. Lillian P. 1947 (Box 5)
- Endowment Fund vs. Page & Holloway 1927-1928 (Box 5)
- Engineering Building 1934 (Box 5)
- Engineering Building-Correspondence 1934-1936 (Box 6)
- Engineering Building-Issue of Bonds 1934-1935 (Box 6)
- Engineering Building-Requisition 1 1934 (Box 6)
- Engineering Building-Requisition 2 1934 (Box 6)
- Engineering Building-Requisition 3 1934 (Box 6)
- Engineering Building-Requisition 4 1934 (Box 6)
- Engineering Building-Requisition 5 1935-1936 (Box 6)
- Ergenbright, R. Granville 1946 (Box 6)
- Faculty Apartments 1922 (Box 6)
- Fayerweather Will 1916-1917 (Box 6)
- Federal Income Tax 1931 (Box 6)
- Folkes, E.J.-Estate 1935 (Box 6)
- Glinn, Mrs. Betty Booker 1925-1930 (Box 7)
- Glover, Mary C. - Estate 1932 (Box 7)
- Goodwyn, Dora H. - Estate 1934-1935 (Box 7)
- Graveure, Louis 1921-1922 (Box 7)
- Greene, Dr. B.W.-Estate 1914-1925 (Box 7)
- Gymnasium 1921-1924 (Box 7)
- Hall, Franklin S. 1931 (Box 7)
- Hartford Insurance Company 1928 (Box 7)
- Hoffman, Mr. S.L. 1928 (Box 7)
- Hopkins, Dr. William E. 1915-1916 (Box 7)
- Hopkins Society 1928 [1938] (Box 7)
- Hospital Contracts 1916-1941 (Box 7)
- Hospital Psychiatric Ward 1938 (Box 7)
- Hospital Wing 4881 - Additional Loan & Grant Agreement 1936 (Box 7)
- Hospital Wing 4881 - 1st Meeting Board of Visitors 1935 (Box 7)
- Hospital Wing 4881 - 2nd Meeting Board of Visitors 1935 (Box 7)
- Hospital Wing 4881 - 1st Requisition 1935 (Box 8)
- Hospital Wing 4881 - 2nd Requisition 1935 (Box 8)
- Hospital Wing 4881 - Miscellaneous 1934-1938 (Box 8)
- Hospital - Proposed Addition 1957 (Box 8)
- Imboden, Leonard 1916 (Box 8)
- James, Edward W. 1908-1933 (Box 8)
- Johnson, Wills-Estate 1923-1926 [1951] (Box 8)
- Kelly, James Downing 1917-1918 (Box 8)
- King Greenhouses 1932 (Box 8)
- Lambeth Field Streets 1927 (Box 8)
- Lefevre, Dr. Alfred 1925 (Box 8)
- Loon, A. Matacia 1925 (Box 8)
- Macconochie, Arthur F. 1932 [1938] (Box 8)
- McIntyre, Richard H. 1928-1947 (Box 8)
- MacIver, Mrs. Randall 1928-1931 (Box 8)
- McKim, Dr. Randolph H. - Estate 1920-1944 (Box 8)
- Madison Hall 1931 (Box 9)
- Malcolm S. Councill Trust 1949 (Box 9)
- Maphis, Chas G. 1934-1935 [1943] (Box 9)
- Marshall, Mrs. Johanna M.-Estate 1939-1940 (Box 9)
- Medical School 1927-1928 (Box 9)
- Medical School-H.E. Crook Company, Inc. 1927-1928 (Box 9)
- Medical School-Johnson-Longworth Hearting Co. 1927 (Box 9)
- Medical School Merger 1922 (Box 9)
- Medical School-Richardson-Wayland Electrical Corporation 1927 (Box 9)
- Merrick, W. Gordon 1910 (Box 9)
- Miller, Lizzie B. 1936-1951 (Box 9)
- Miscellaneous 1915-1942 (Box 9)
- Mountain Lake 1932-1941 (Box 9)
- Mullen, Mrs. William B. 1932 (Box 9)
- National Geographic Society 1939 (Box 10)
- Navy Research Laboratory 1940 (Box 10)
- Newcomb, Dr. J.L. 1939-1943 (Box 10)
- Nurses' Home 1930 (Box 10)
- Nurses' Home Addition 1944 (Box 10)
- Page, Dr. J.M. 1928 (Box 10)
- Page, Lucy W. & Mildred N. 1934-1961 (Box 10)
- Pantops 1929-1947 (Box 10)
- Parrish, Robert P. - Estate 1916-1918 (Box 10)
- Payne, Oliver H. 1917 (Box 10)
- Phi Sigma Kappa Fraternity - Column Club 1958 (Box 10)
- Public Health Board 1922-1923 (Box 10)
- Raffman, Halsey 1931 (Box 10)
- Randolph, Walter - Estate 1936-1937 (Box 10)
- Richmond, Edward Dean - Estate 1933 (Box 10)
- Rixey, Admiral Presley M.- Estate 1935-1936 (Box 10)
- Rogers, Floyd & Page, J.M. 1927 (Box 11)
- Rogers, James M. 1915 (Box 11)
- Ryan, Scholarships 1926-1938 (Box 11)
- Schwab, David-Estate 1935-1936 (Box 11)
- Sewers 1927-1931 (Box 11)
- Shields, Mrs. Mazyck Wilson - Estate 1943-1945 (Box 11)
- Shields, Mazyck Wilson - Estate, Florida Lands 1944-1945 (Box 11)
- Shields, Mazyck Wilson - Estate, Transfer of UVa. Stocks 1944-1945 (Box 11)
- Shields, Mazyck Wilson - Estate, VMI 1943-1945 (Box 11)
- Silverstein, A.E. 1933 (Box 11)
- Sinclair, Cephas-Estate 1921-1929 (Box 11)
- Smith, Mrs. Mary Amelia - Estate 1912-1946 (Box 11)
- Smith, W. Lawrence - Claim 1915-1916 (Box 11)
- Spratt Coal Company 1925-1930 (Box 12)
- Stanfield, Theodore - Estate 1938-1946 (Box 12)
- Steele, Charles - Estate 1941 (Box 12)
- Stephenson, Dr. J.W. 1925-1926 (Box 12)
- Stitt, Laura Carter - Estate 1936 (Box 12)
- Taliaferro, Whitmell T. - Estate 1934-1936, 2 folders (Box 12)
- Taylor, Archibald H. 1941-1944 (Box 12)
- Thompson, Judge Uly O. 1935-1936 (Box 13)
- Thorne, Joel W. - Estate 1944 (Box 13)
- Thornton, Miss Jane 1930-1931 (Box 13)
- Thurman, Francis S. 1940-1941 (Box 13)
- Tree, Lambert - Estate 1910 (Box 13)
- Virginia Public Service Co. 1944 (Box 13)
- Virginia Quarterly Review 1931-1943 (Box 13)
- Virginia Safe Department & Trust Corp. 1906 (Box 13)
- Virginia Trust Co. 1947 (Box 13)
- Waddy Estate 1929-1933 (Box 13)
- Wandless, Dr. Henry W.-Estate 1934 (Box 13)
- Williams, Mrs. Cora B.-Estate 1924 (Box 13)
- Wilson, Thomas a. 1925-1927 (Box 13)
- Workmen's Compensation 1932 (Box 13)
- Y.M.C.A. 1946 (Box 13)
- Zinn, George - Estate 1929-1931 (Box 13)
- Zoning Changes 1943-1944 (Box 13)